http://www.pdftron.com/privacy/

Some test text!menuTechnologykeyboard_arrow_downDocumentationkeyboard_arrow_downSolutionskeyboard_arrow_downCompanykeyboard_arrow_downSupportkeyboard_arrow_downBlogContact SalesFree TrialPDFPDFchevron_rightOfficeMS Officechevron_rightCADCADchevron_rightVideoVideochevron_rightMoreMore File Typeschevron_rightAll platforms, one APIWebAndroidiOSWindowsXamarinLinuxPDFTron PDF SDKOverviewAnnotationViewerConversionForm FillingEdit & ManipulateDocument AnalysisOCRParsing and ExtractionDigital SignaturesRedactionMeasuring ToolsMore functionalityWebchevron_rightAndroidchevron_rightiOSchevron_rightWindowschevron_rightLinuxchevron_rightmacOSchevron_rightWebOverviewGuidesAPISamplesLaunch DemoFrameworksReactAngularElectronNode.jsMore frameworks...IntegrationsSalesforceMendixSharePointIndustriesArchitecture, Engineering, ConstructionFinanceGovernmentHealthcareLegalPharma & Life SciencesAbout UsCustomersLicensingLeadershipWebinarsCareersContact UsLearningResourcesSubscriptionPrivacy PolicyLast Modified: July 27, 2020PDFTron Systems Inc. (“PDFTron”, “we”, “us”, “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) describes what Personal Information (as defined below) and other information we may collect from you when you visit this website (“Site”), how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, as well as the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure of that information to other parties.
We strongly urge you to read this policy from beginning to end.This policy is provided in a layered format for ease of access.
Click on the table of content to jump to a specific section.Overview and ScopeInformation We May Collect From YouHow We Use Your Personal InformationDisclosure of Your InformationWhere We Store Your Personal InformationConsent and Other Legal Basis For Collection, Use, and Disclosure of Personal InformationIs My Personal Information Secure?Retention of Personal InformationChildrenThird Party LinksYour RightsChanges To Our Privacy PolicyContact UsOVERVIEW AND SCOPEWe believe that you should always know what data we collect from you, how we use it, and that you should have meaningful control over both. This policy describes how we use Personal Information, with whom we share it, your rights and choices, and how you can contact us about our privacy practices.INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU“Personal Information” is information about an identifiable individual, such as their name, mailing address, email address, or phone number, personal description, or photograph, whether used alone, or when combined with other personal or identifying information which is linked or linkable to a specific individual.We may collect and process the following information about you through the Site:Information you give usPlease remember that you control what Personal Information you provide to us while visiting the Site. You can visit the Site without registering or providing any Personal Information at all.You may give us Personal Information about you through the Site:by filling in forms on our Site;by registering to use our Site or using our services, products and tools we make available for use on our Site;by registering for webinars;by using our support chat function on our Site to correspond with us in connection with your use of our Site;by participating in blogs, discussion boards or other social media functions on our Site;by entering a competition, promotion or survey on our Site;when you report a problem with our Site; orif you upload a file to our services, products, demos or tools on our Site. In addition to the information you provide as the file, we may collect and process the following information during the uploading and processing process:IP address; anddate and time.Information we automatically collect on this SiteIP Addresses and Click-Stream DataWith regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically collect the following information:technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our Site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.The Site uses Mouseflow: a third party website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns, and similar features/functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar meta data. Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you'd like to opt-out, you can do so at https://mouseflow.com/opt-out. If you'd like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at privacy@mouseflow.com.The information collected cannot typically be used to identify you personally. However, if you have specifically informed us of your identity (for example by registering for something or providing us with your contact information through the Site, it may be possible for us to link certain information to information that identifies you personally. Digital Markers (including Cookies), Online Tracking Technologies, Online Interest Based AdvertisingA digital marker is created by a website visitor’s Internet browser to maintain certain pieces of information for the website to reference during the same or subsequent visits. Examples of digital markers are cookies or HTML5 Web storage. Among other things, digital markers can allow a website to recognize a previous visit each time the visitor accesses the website, and track what information is viewed on a website.We use sessional and persistent digital markers on some portions of the Site. Digital markers are created when you visit our Site. Sessional markers exist while you remain on our website, and persistent markers continue to exist after you have left our website.For information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy.Similarly, we or our third-party service providers/advertisers may also use "web beacons,” “pixel tags” or other tracking technologies, which are typically small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor behaviour and collect certain data regarding the actions of our guests online. These digital markers and other technologies may be used to track across time, sites, and devices. For example, these technologies can be used to analyze your online traffic patterns, to enhance your experience when using the Site, to store information during your session, to personalize the Site for you based on your preferences and selections, to target advertising or content to you (as described further below) and to collect information about you and your visit to the Site for other marketing and business purposes. You may adjust your privacy preferences regarding the use of digital markers, including cookies, and similar technologies through your browser.
However, disabling cookies may impair your user experience and disable certain features of the Site.
Data about your activities online may be collected for use in providing advertising tailored to your individual interests, either by us, or third parties. We may work with third parties such as network advertisers and ad exchanges to serve advertisements across the internet and may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party websites and viewing of ads and of our content. We and these third-party vendors, including Google and LinkedIn, may use third-party technologies (such as the LinkedIn Insight Tag) together with our own first party technologies in order to analyze ad impressions, your use of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services. The information collected may also include information about your visits to the Site, include the pages you have viewed and what content you have seen. These third-party tracking technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times; and (c) understand the effectiveness of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. You can opt out of certain advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics opt out browser add on. If you wish to take steps to opt-out of tracking by certain online advertisers, you can visit the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page at https://www.aboutads.info/choices or the Network Advertising Initiative at https://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp. To learn more about how to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, visit Google’s Ads Settings, here. To learn more about cookies and similar tracking technologies, and how they can affect your privacy, visit allaboutcookies.org. To learn more about, or to opt-out of Google’s analytic and marketing services, visit the Google Privacy Notice.
LinkedIn members can control the use of their Personal Information for advertising purposes through their account settings.Information we receive from other sourcesWe may receive information about you if you use any of the other websites we operate or the other online projects or services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, technical and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers) and may receive information about you from them.
We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you through the Site to create combined information.HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe use Personal Information to:provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us through the Site;carry out any agreements entered into between you and us through the Site;respond to inquiries or service requests and monitor such responses;manage our relationship with you;subject to applicable laws, provide information about and market our products or services or products or services of third parties, and inform you of offers or new features that we believe may be of interest to you.
If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us, you may opt-out via the unsubscribe link included in such emails.
Please note that if you opt-out of receiving marketing-related emails from us,
we may still send you important administrative messages that are required to provide you with our services and we nonetheless reserve the right to contact you (including by e-mail or text) where we are legally required or permitted to do so;we reserve the right to send you important administrative messages that are required to provide you with our services;to notify you about changes to our Site;resolve problems;manage the Site and assess usage;enhance or personalize your experience using our Site;inform you of offers or new features that we believe may be of interest to you;process or maintain your subscription to a newsletter or mailing list;facilitate various programs, promotions or contests in which you participate;target advertising or content, or for other advertising, promotional or marketing purposes;study the use and popularity of various areas of our Site and to improve our Sites; analyze general locations where our content is viewed (by reviewing IP addresses);to administer our Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;to improve our Site, products and services and to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; to allow you to participate in interactive features of our Site, when you choose to do so;as part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure.We may also use such information for other purposes related to our business or that of our related entities, as well as for any other purpose described in this policy or any other agreement you may enter with us or otherwise as we may disclose to you or to which you consent from time to time, or for other purposes as required or permitted by applicable law.DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATIONWe may share your Personal Information with any member of our corporate group, which means our subsidiaries, our parent company and its subsidiaries.We do not sell or rent Personal Information to marketers or unaffiliated third parties.
We may share your information with selected third parties including:business partners and suppliers when this is necessary to provide our services to our users or for the performance of any contract we enter into with you;advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.
Such disclosures are typically aggregate information about our users and analyses of our server logs, traffic, or information relating to customer leads, including details regarding usage of the Site and general information about our audience, and are not generally considered to be Personal Information;analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our Site;our service providers who provide certain services on our behalf such as data hosting or processing services.
We will use contractual arrangements to protect Personal Information disclosed to these service provider;in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets or (subject to confidentiality restrictions) during the due diligence process, in accordance with applicable law;if PDFTron or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case Personal Information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets, in accordance with applicable law;if we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or as we believe in good faith may be reasonably necessary to comply with any law, regulation, rule, court order, or other lawful requests from governmental, regulatory or administrative agencies or law enforcement authorities (including in response to law enforcement or national security requirements), or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use, and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of PDFTron, our customers, or others; as otherwise may be required or permitted by applicable law.WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONPDFTron is based in Canada and the information (including any Personal Information) we collect is transferred, maintained, stored, and processed in Canada and other countries outside Canada where our or our service providers’ facilities may be located, including the United States. You understand and agree that we may store and process the information you provide to us in Canada and other countries. The data protection and privacy laws in those countries may offer a lower level of protection than the data protection and privacy laws of your country.
Also, this information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in Canada and foreign countries according to their laws.If you are located in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, we comply with applicable laws to provide an adequate level of data protection for the transfer of your Personal Information outside of the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the United States.CONSENT AND OTHER LEGAL BASIS FOR COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONBy using our Site and providing Personal Information to us, you voluntarily consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information as specified in this policy.
Without limiting the foregoing, we may on occasion ask you to consent when we collect, use, or disclose your Personal Information in specific circumstances, in which case we may ask for your consent in writing (including by electronic means) although in some circumstances we may accept your oral consent.
Sometimes your consent will be implied through your conduct with us if the purpose of the collection, use or disclosure is obvious and you voluntarily provide the information.Depending on your location and subject to applicable law, we may use your Personal Information for the purposes set forth in this policy based on other legal grounds including:your consent;to carry out the performance of a contract or because you have asked us to take steps in order to enter into a contract;our legitimate business interests, including:managing our relationship with you;direct marketing;product development and enhancement; information, system, network, and cyber security;general corporate operations and due diligence; to comply with a legal obligation and/or defend against legal claims;to protect a vital interest of the individual.In addition, we may collect, use, and disclose personal information without your consent when we are required or permitted by applicable law to do so.IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?We take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information is kept safe from loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.
Among the steps we take in order to protect your information are:premises security;restricted file access to personal information;deploying technological safeguards like security software and firewalls to prevent hacking or unauthorized computer access;internal password and security policies;restricted file access to personal information.Unfortunately, no transmission of information via the internet or storage of information is completely secure. Although we take commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site or that we store.RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATIONPersonal Information will be retained in accordance with this policy for as long as may be necessary or relevant for the purpose of collection, or as may be required or permitted by applicable law, after which time it may be made anonymous or destroyed unless you further consent to its continued retention.CHILDRENThe Site is not intended or directed to children under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information relating to children or track their use of the Site.THIRD PARTY LINKSOur Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites including those of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.
If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.
Please check these policies before you submit any Personal Information to these websites.YOUR RIGHTSAccess to and correction of Personal InformationYou have a right to request access to your Personal Information and to request a correction to it if you believe it is inaccurate. If you have submitted Personal Information to us and would like to have access to it, or if you would like to have it corrected, please contact us using the contact information provided below. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request; however, in some cases we may not be able to allow you to access certain Personal Information in certain circumstances, for example if it contains Personal Information of other persons, or for legal reasons. We may require you to verify your identity before you access your personal information.Withdrawal of consentIndividuals have the right to withdraw their consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of Personal Information at any time, except where that withdrawal would frustrate the performance of a legal obligation by us.
Upon reasonable written notice given to us, all Personal Information held by us that is identifiable to that individual will be removed from our records and a notice of the impact of that removal will be provided to the individual.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you withdraw consent we nonetheless reserves the right to retain, collect, use and disclose Personal Information without your consent where we are required or permitted by applicable law to do so.Your data protection rightsDepending on your location and subject to applicable law, you may have additional rights with respect to your Personal Information, including: “Right to be forgotten” - the right to request that we erase your Personal Information in certain circumstances provided by applicable law; “Data portability” - the right to request that we send to another company, where technically feasible, your Personal Information; the right to request that we restrict the processing of your Personal Information in certain circumstances; for example, if you contest the accuracy of the Personal Information while we are verifying the accuracy; the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing having impact on rights.In order to exercise these rights, you may contact us as described in the Contact Us section below.
We will comply with your request to the extent required by applicable law.
If you feel that you have not received a satisfactory response from us, you may consult with the data protection authority in your country.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYAny changes we may make to our policy in the future will be posted on this page. The date this policy was last revised is identified on the top of this page.
Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our policy.CONTACT USQuestions, comments and requests regarding this policy may be addressed to info@pdftron.com.closeFree TrialGet unlimited trial usage of PDFTron SDK to bring accurate, reliable, and fast document processing capabilities to any application or workflow.Select a platform to get started with your free trial.WebAndroidiOSWindowsLinuxIntegrate via NPMManual integrationReactAngularCordovaElectronVueSvelteBlazorTypeScriptNode.jsSalesforceUnlimited usage. No email address required.Join our upcoming webinar to find out about built-in, full-functioning document capabilities directly in Salesforce.Save your seatcloseTECHNOLOGYPDFMS OfficeCADVideoMore File TypesPlatformsDEVELOPERSDocumentationSupportPDFNet ForumWebViewer ForumLearningCOMPANYAbout UsCustomersLeadership TeamBrand AssetsPDFTron for StartupsStay in touchBlogLicensingCareersContact UsCOPYRIGHT 2001-2020 PDFTRON SYSTEMS, INC.PrivacyTerms of Use
